Anastasia Yaskevich

Android Developer

Minsk, Belarus anastasia.yaskevich@gmail.com +375 (29) 352-69-32

SUMMARY

I am Android developer for more than 1 year and more than 4 years in software engineering in total. Worked both as solo developer and in a team, supported existing apps and created new ones from scratch. Also have remote work experience. Familiar with such tools as Jira, Git, Figma, Invision. English level is Intermediate+.

EDUCATION

09/2011 — 06/2016

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Specialist's Degree in Computer Systems and Networks. Got specialization of Sotfware for Information Technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

11/2018 — 03/2019

Android Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a betting mobile application. Used Kotlin, MVI, Clean Architecture, Retrofit, RxJava 2, Dagger 2, JUnit and Mockito for unit testing. Done part of performance optimization of UI.

03/2018 — 11/2018

Android Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a client mobile application. Used Kotlin, Retrofit, Room, RxJava 2, Dagger 2, MVP, Clean Architecture. Took part in implementation of Form Decorator (transformed JSON of field appearance description into UI)

07/2016 — 03/2018

Frontend Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a betting mobile web application on React.js and ES6, Redux. Refactoring and support of Android wrapper app on Crosswalk.

11/2015 — 07/2016

Groovy Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a large web application. Worked in a team of 6 developers and 4 QA engineers. Used technologies: Groovy & Grails, MySQL, CoffeeScript, AngularJS, Redis.

02/2015 — *11/2015*

Junior Groovy Developer at REID Consulting

Creating small web applications from scratch. Used Groovy & Grails and Jenkins as CI. Also implemented all the frontend part.